Cole, David L. Papers 5588
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Twenty-fifth Anniversary Meeting of the National Academy of Arbitrators, 1971 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  Dayton, Ohio; contains speech, "An Inductive Analysis of Labor-Management Attitudes Revisited
- All Labor Mediators Assemble (ALMA) Conference, 1972 (Box 204, Folder 9)
  Saratoga Springs, New York; contains anecdotes and notes by Cole
- Collective Bargaining Forum, 1973 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  San Francisco, California; includes speech and speech notes
- Society of Professionals in Dispute Resolution Inaugural Convention, 1973 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  Virginia; includes speech and speech notes
- National Chamber of Commerce dinner meeting of Labor Relations Committee, 1973 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  Washington, District of Columbia; includes paper "Collective Bargaining and Industrial Peace" by Mr. Cole
- Federal Mediation and Conciliation Seminar, 1973 (Box 205, Folder 4)
  Washington, District of Columbia; includes speech "New Inroads in Achieving Industrial Peace"
- New York Bar Association Seminar, 1973 (Box 205, Folder 5)
- Sol Stetin (International President of the Textile Workers Union of America) dinner, 1973 (Box 205, Folder 6)
  New York City; speech made by Cole
- Industrial Relations Research Association Annual Meeting, 1973 (Box 205, Folder 7)
  New York City; contains Cole's speech "Role of the National Commission for Industrial Peace"
- New York University School of Business and Public Administration, 1974 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  Key Issue Lecture Series, 1974; includes Cole's paper "Is Industrial Peace Achievable?"
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies, 1977 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  Sessions on Article XX, 1977; includes copy of article, correspondence, and notes
- Miscellaneous speeches; notes and copies (Box 206, Folder 3)
- The Quest for Industrial Peace, 1963 (Box 206.1, Folder All)
  Book by Cole; includes book notes, market survey for book, and "thank you" letters for autographed copies
- Martin Luther King Committee of Harvard Law School, 1968 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  Cole was a member of Support Committee
- Harvard Club of New York City (Box 207, Folder 2)
  Cole elected as member
- Harvard College Fund, Class of Nineteen twenty-one (Box 207, Folder 3)
  Includes donation receipts
- Harvard Law School Fund (Box 207, Folder 4)
  Donation receipts
- Harvard University Trade Union Program, 1962-1967 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  1962 - 1963, 1965 - 1966, 1966 - 1967; includes programs, notes and papers
- Sesquicentennial Fund of the Harvard Law School (Box 207, Folder 6)
- Harvard School Fund Solicitations, Twenty-fifth annual giving (Box 208, Folder 1)
  Includes donation receipts and correspondence
- Harvard Class of Nineteen Twenty-one's fiftieth reunion, 1971 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  Cambridge, Massachusetts; includes Cole's personal history and vita
- Sesquicentennial Fund of the Harvard Law School (Box 208, Folder 3)
- Harvard Law School Fund (Box 209, Folder 1)
  Donation receipts, etc.
- Bitumous Coal Letter from President Truman to Economic Stabilization Administrator (Box 210, Folder 1)
- Meeting on Collective Bargaining in the Steel Industry, 1959 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  Washington, District of Columbia
- Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1972-1974 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  Data on endowment
- Carnegie Endowment (Special Subcommittee), 1975 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  Investigation of Endowment's past relationship with Walter Leyes and Lee Harris (kickback scheme)
- Defense Savings Committee, 1942 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  Information regarding defense savings bonds and employee authorization cards
- Defense Plant Corporation (DPC), 1944 (Box 211, Folder 2)
  Newspaper clippings regarding thirty-eight DPC plants in New Jersey which were to be sold to prospective buyers when no longer needed in war effort
- Jack Golodner (Box 211, Folder 3)
  Includes business transactions between Golodner and Cole and "No-Raid Agreement" joint project
- Harry B. Haines (Box 211, Folder 4)
  New Printing Company and The Patterson Evening News; Cole on leave of absence as Patterson, New Jersey counsel; making arrangements to return to that position from White House; H. Haines, a personal friend, reported on Cole's activities in Patterson Evening News
- Hassenfeld Brothers (Box 211, Folder 5)
  John Hand and Sons; disagreement regarding bill of sale between above parties; includes letters to Cole soliciting his help
- Humble Oil, 1963 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  Requested Cole to meet with management regarding grievance procedures, 1963
- Jack J. Kohoe (Box 211, Folder 7)
  Cole as advisor on deed to house
- Metropolitan Opera dispute, 1969 (Box 211, Folder 8)
  1969 season; correspondence regarding Cole's mediation of the dispute
- The Philharmonic Society of Northern New Jersey (Box 211, Folder 9)
  Cole collected pledges to the Society
- Mutual Security Agency (Box 211, Folder 10)
  Regarding Cole's appointment as member of United States Advisory Group on European Productivity
- Prudential Fabrics, 1960 (Box 211, Folder 11)
  Nathan Cohen left shares of above stock to his wife and, upon her death, to Cole
- Rutgers University, 1965 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  Cole was trustee (resigned February 1965); includes his papers
- Dr. James T. Shotwell, 1955 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  Carnegie Endowment for International Peace
- Robert Spruengli (Box 212, Folder 3)
  President of Lindt and Spruengli Limited Chocolate Works, Zurich, Switzerland, regarding Cole's interest in merging American chocolate manufacturer with above party
- Tour books and souvenirs from Japan (Box 212, Folder 4)
- Newspaper clippings on labor relations (Box 213, Folder 1)
  Concentration on the steel industry
- Sweden (Box 213, Folder 2)
  Labor relations in research materials used by President's Advisory Committee on Labor-Management Policy
- Textile Workers Union of America, 1964 (Box 213, Folder 3)
  Supplementary Vacation Fund; Cole named "Umpire in the Deed of Trust"
- United Airlines, 1964 (Box 213, Folder 4)
  Letter of agreement regarding panel to be used in deadlocked cases
- Miscellaneous charts and publications (Box 213, Folder 5)
  Includes job specifications for the textile industry
- Report to President of the United States, 1961 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  By Cole and others regarding labor disputes in maritime industry